Stafford, Ronald B.; Papers apap217
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislation, 1974-2002; 9; 32.51 cubic ft.
  - Increase Witness Attendance Fees and Travel Expenses, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 30)
  - Three Year Limit on Study of a River, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 31)
  - Practicality of a Notice of Motion for a Temporary Restraining Order, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 32)
  - Discovery in Cases Based Upon a Simplified Information Charging a Misdemeanor, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 33)
  - Creation of a Keeseville Industrial Development Agency, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 34)
  - Town of Altamont Bond Issuance, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 35)
  - Overrule Holdings Dealing with Exclusive Delays and Defaults, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 36)
  - Issuance of Certain Subpoenas, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 37)
  - Classify Assault on a Public Servant a Felony, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 38)
  - Notice of Default Judgment, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 39)
  - Contract to Make a Joint Will Requirements, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 40)
  - Increase Weekly Disability Amount for Firemen, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 41)
  - Partial Reimbursement of Registration Fees, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 42)
  - Division for Youth Temporary Releases, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 43)
  - Aid for School Districts with Native American Pupils, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 44)
  - Legislative Approval of the Adirondack Park Master Plan, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 45)
  - Insurance Coverage of Snowmobiles, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 46)
  - Issues of Fact that Arise Upon an Application to Compel or Stay Arbitration will be Tried without a Jury, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 47)
  - Civil Defense Powers of Peace Officers Under the Defense Emergency Act, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 48)
  - Reimbursement for Mandatory Full Value Assessments of Real Property, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 49)
  - Heart Disability/Retirement and Social Security Law, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 50)
  - Article 78 Proceedings Transferred to the Appellate Division, 1983 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 51)
  - Two Year Term for the Warren County ORDA Member, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 52)
  - Reimbursement for Fire Assistance in Adirondack Park, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 53)
  - Transfer OGS Abandoned Railroad Bed to the Three Point Two Corporation, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 54)
  - Increase Time Allowed for Legible Hospital Records Recreation, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 55)
  - Single Trial of Separate Defendants Charged with Separate Crimes from an Act or Series of Acts, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 56)
  - Physician-Patient and Psychologist-Client Privileges, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 57)
  - Deer Management Permit and Hunting Seasons, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 58)
  - Degree Requirements for the Nursing Profession, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 59)
  - Town of Jay Industrial Development Agency, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 60)
  - Provide a Definition for "Dangerous Drugs", 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 61)
  - Point Au Roche State Park Development Appropriation, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 62)
  - Permit Use of Prior Youthful Offender Adjudications if they were Felony Convictions, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 63)
  - Mandatory and Consecutive Sentences for Most Bail Jumping and Escape Offenses, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 64)
  - More Realistic Time Periods in Certain Disclosure Proceedings, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 65)
  - Provide a Discovery Statute of Limitations Rule for Toxic Torts, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 66)
  - Allow Prisoners Serving Life Sentences to Marry without Restriction, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 67)
  - Glens Falls Land Exchange, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 68)
  - Three Year Budget, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 69)
  - Community Dispute Resolution Centers Program, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 70)
  - Restriction of Telephone Solicitation, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 71)
  - Allows a Recorded Oral Statement for Acts of Insurance Fraud, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 72)
  - Service of Papers in Third Party Practice, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 73)
  - Transportation of Firearms, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 74)
  - Complaints on Unlawful Discrimination, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 75)
  - Notice of Prisoner Release to a Sheriff with Prior Custody, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 76)
  - Allow for an Appeal from a Pretrail Oder, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 77)
  - Procedure to Obtain a Search Warrant for Direction a Search for and Seizure of a Person, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 78)
  - Right to Refuse to Consent to the Discharge of Alternate Jurors, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 79)
  - Availability of Dispositions, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 80)
  - Require Personal Delivery to the Attorney General's Office for an Article 78 Proceeding Against the State, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 81)
  - Disposition and Destruction of Gambling Devices, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 82)
  - Matching Funds to Promote Business and Economic Development, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 83)
  - Payment of Bonuses to Korean and Vietnam Veterans, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 84)
  - Free Muzzle Loading Stamps for Certain Disabled Veterans, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 85)
  - Modification of the Civil Jurisdiction of the Court of Appeals, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 86)
  - Improvement of Wildlife Habitat, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 87)
  - Criminal Leave Applications and Civil Leave Procedures, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 88)
  - Interest on Secured Loans, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 89)
  - Interest on Secure Loans or Forbearances, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 90)
  - Examination of Presentence Reports by the DA and Prosecutor, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 91)
  - Construction Expenses for Rouse Point Bridge, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 92-93)
  - Prison Cost Reimbursement, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 94)
  - Gathering of Dead Wood from State-Owned Forest Land, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 95)
  - Discharge of Treated Sewage into the Lake George Basin, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 96)
  - Records and Reports of Persons Committed to or Placed with the Division of Youth, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 97)
  - Gross Receipts Tax Exemption, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 98)
  - Judgements Against Out of State Residents, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 99)
  - Wildlife Habitat Management, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 100)
  - Felonies that Eavesdropping Warrant May be Issued for, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 101)
  - Senior Citizen Bingo, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 102)
  - Create a Small Stream Clearing and Stabilization Program, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 103)
  - Restitution Payments to the Estate of Deceased Victims, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 104)
  - "Fingerprintable" Offenses, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 105)
  - Clarify the Circumstances in which Probation Departments must Release Pre-Sentencing Reports, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 106)
  - Powers of Safety Officers in In-Patient Facilities of Mental Health, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 107)
  - Delay Utilization of Reduced Assessments on State Lands by One Year when a Town hasn't been given Proper Notice, 1984 (Box 13 (9-Legislation), Folder 108)
  - Increase Criminal Penalties and Civil Remedies for Counterfeiting Trademarks, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - Designation of the Louis J. Lefkowitz State Office Building, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - Require Abatement of a Public/Private Nuisance Against a Violation of the Environmental Conservation Law, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - Hiking Trail from Battery Park to Mount Mercy Peak, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - Reimburse Whitehall Central School District for State Aid Lost During Flood Closure, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - Eliminates Requirement that Pre-Sentence Reports be Submitted where Parties Agree on the Sentence, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - Require Sanitary Facilities Aboard Crafts on Lake Champlain, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - Allow for Videotaped Testimony in Lieu of Live Testimony, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - State Route 3 Designation as Passing Through Saranac Lake, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 9)
  - Prefunded Funeral Services, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - Jurisdiction over Landlords, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - Changing the Sentence Structure for Certain Class A Misdemeanors, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - Allow Eavesdropping Warrants for Felonies Under the General Business Archive, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - Eliminate the Need to Return Parole Violators to State Correctional Facilities in certain cases, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - Require Public Office Candidates to be Specific and Precise when Citing Another Candidate's Voting Record, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - Workers' Compensation, Physicians as Co-Employees, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 16)
  - Issuance of Subpoenas upon a Municipal Corporation, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - Full Disability Coverage for Correction Officers, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 18)
  - Provide Necessary Funds for the Adirondack Local Government Review Board, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - Disability for Correctional Officers, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - Defining the Owner of Real Property for Notice of Tax Sale, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - Procedure and Circumstances for a Violation of a Parole Hearing, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - New Offenses Involving Computer Crimes, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - Delinquent Restitution and Reparation Payments, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 24)
  - Allows Vending Machines at Rest Areas, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - Mandatory Surcharges and the Collecting Authority, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 26)
  - Essex County Highway Realignment, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 27)
  - Increase County Clerks Salaries, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 28)
  - Automatic Access to Sealed Records for Probation Departments, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 29)
  - Tier III Retirement Plan Voluntary Contributions, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 30)
  - 100th Anniversary of the State Forest Preserve, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 31-32)
  - Beer Brewers and Imports Selling Beer in New York State Must Designate a Geographic Area for its Wholesalers/Distributors, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 33)
  - Certain Membership in the New York State Retirement System, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 34)
  - Simplify the Procedure for the Service and Filing of a Claim in the Court of Appeals, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 35)
  - Permit Court of Claims to Levy a Sanction Against an Attorney, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 36)
  - Minimize the Number of Court Appearances an Identification Witness Must Make, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 37)
  - Creation of the Champlain Industrial Development Agency, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 38)
  - Promote Increased Statewide Prosecution of Conduct that is Hazardous to Public Health Safety, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 39)
  - Include the Use of a Credit Card for Illegal Purpose as Forgery in the Second Degree, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 40)
  - Issuance of Arrest Warrants for Defendant's Who Have Escaped the Custody of the Mental Health Commissioner, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 41)
  - Require Consent of the People before a Jury Trial may be Waived, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 42)
  - Procedures for Defendants Committed to the State Commissioner of Mental Health's Custody, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 43)
  - Forest Management Areas, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 44)
  - Exclude Olympic Doctors from New York State Licensure Requirements, 1984 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 45)
  - Reimbursement for Costs of Maintaining Prisoners in County and City Facilities, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 46)
  - Reimbursement for Mandated Full Value Assessment, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 47)
  - Income Tax Reduction for Those who Adopt a Child, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 48)
  - Permit Pistols and Revolvers During Archery/Muzzle-Loading Deer Season, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 49)
  - Property Insurance Policies to Include Chipmunk Damages, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 50)
  - Introduction of Affidavits, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 51)
  - New OTBs, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 52)
  - State Reimbursement for Continuing Aide of Ineligible Recipients, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 53)
  - Holding of Precious Metals, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 54)
  - Remove Youth Employment Monetary Limits, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 55)
  - Legislative Power to Approve or Disapprove the State Land Master Plan, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 56)
  - Creation of the Code of Evidence, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 57)
  - Improve Proceedings Governing the Use of Bills of Particulars, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 58)
  - Licensing of Competent Tour Guides, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 59)
  - Direct Deposit of State Employees' Paychecks, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 60)
  - DEC Regulations of Pesticide Spraying in the Adirondack Park, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 61)
  - Validating Date Tags for Motorboats, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 62)
  - Creation of a New Offense of Aggravated Harassment in the Third Degree, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 63)
  - Division of State Police Transportation and Concealment of Illegal Gambling, Lottery, or Policy Scheme Records, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 64)
  - Jurisdiction of State Highways in Washington County, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 65)
  - Senior Real Property Tax Exemption, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 66)
  - Exempt Seasonal Employees from Minimum Wage Provisions, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 67)
  - Taxing State Lands Operated by the DEC as Public Campsites, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 68)
  - Provide State Aid for Computerized Fleet Maintenance Services, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 69)
  - Tax Credit for Using Another Form of Heating Fuel, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 70)
  - Maintenance of Wildlife Habitat in the Forest Preserve, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 71)
  - Volunteer Licensed Physicians at the Olympic Events at Lake Placid, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 72)
  - Payment of Restitution and Reparation, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 73)
  - Exempts Clothing for Human Use from Sales Tax, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 74)
  - Insurance Coverage for Treatment of Mental, Nervous or Emotional Disorders, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 75)
  - Eligibility Requirements for Unemployment, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 76)
  - Re-Evaluation of APA Master Plan, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 77)
  - Review of the Acquisition of Control of Brokers and Dealers by the Attorney General, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 78)
  - Providing Assistance for Public Radio Stations in Rochester and Plattsburgh, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 79)
  - DMV Registration Partial Refunds, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 80)
  - Notice to Taxpayers of Federal Request for Mandatory Disclosure of State Tax Records, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 81)
  - Provide Prior Statements to a Defendant when he Testifies, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 82)
  - Study of Economic Impact of the APA Development Plan, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 83)
  - Gives Authority to Fix Minimum Periods of Imprisonment to the Sentencing Court, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 84)
  - Refund on Registration Fees for Motor Vehicles, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 85)
  - Extending the Expiration Date of Washington County Solid Waste Management, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 86)
  - Determining if a Prior Youthful Offender Conviction is a Predicate Felony, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 87)
  - Interest of Public Officers in Pari-Mutuel Racing Licenses, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 88)
  - Require the Placement of State Funds in Interest Bearing Accounts, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 89)
  - Glens Falls Industrial Development Agency Members as Directors of Banks, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 90)
  - Making Dude Ranch Trail an Official Scenic Trail, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 91)
  - Three Year Budget, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 92)
  - Gathering of Dead Wood from State-Owned Forest Land, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 93)
  - Raises Limit of Town Indebtedness within the Adirondack Park, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 94)
  - Legislative Power over Proposed Agencies' Rules, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 95)
  - Retired Armed Forces Members Tax Exemption, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 96)
  - Increase Local Assistance to Counties for the Salaries of Full-Time DAs, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 97)
  - Adirondack Park Forest Management Areas, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 98)
  - Washington/Warren County Joint Solid Waste Management Facility, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 99)
  - Creation of the Port Henry Industrial Development Agency, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 100)
  - State Reimbursement for Tax Revenue Losses by Forest Land Exemptions, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 101)
  - Dissolution of the Warren County Sewer District No. 1, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 102)
  - Aid for Public Schools with Native American Pupils, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 103)
  - Saranac Lake Town Highways, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 104)
  - Three Year Study Limit for Rivers, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 105)
  - Financial Security Funds in Vehicles Transporting Passengers for Hire, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 106)
  - Sale of Certain Species of Wildlife, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 107)
  - New York State Business and Economic Development Promotion Act, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 108)
  - Tortious Invasion and Legal/Equitable Relief, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 109)
  - Limitation of the Expert Testimony Offered by a Psychiatrist or Psychologist, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 110)
  - Requires Personal Delivery of Service Against State Bodies or Officers to the Attorney General's Office, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 111)
  - Increase Possible Level of Costs Awarded in Martin Act Cases, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 112)
  - Utilization of Wiretaps and Other Electronic Surveillance Techniques, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 113)
  - Combination Fishing-Big Game Licenses, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 114)
  - Court Proceedings without Council, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 115)
  - Improve Wildlife Habitat in the Adirondack Park Forest Preserve, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 116)
  - Exempt Employers of Alien Agricultural Labor from Paying Unemployment Insurance, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 117)
  - Special Fund for Snowmobile Trail Systems, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 118)
  - Creation of the Adirondack Park Tax District, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 119)
  - Court Issued Sanction by the State Liquor Authority Cannot Exceed 30 Days, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 120)
  - Allow Champlain to Transfer Municipal Park Property to Private Ownership, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 121)
  - Shorten the Required Period of Residency Needed for a Resident License, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 122)
  - Allow Social Services Department to Levy Fee Against Unpaid Child Support Payments, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 123)
  - Removes the Liability of Propane Companies from Paying the Utility Tax, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 124)
  - Improvement of Wildlife Habitat, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 125)
  - Management of State Lands within the Adirondack Park, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 126)
  - New York Income Tax Credit for Income Taxes Already Paid in Quebec/Ontario, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 127)
  - Exempt Organized Camp Employees from Making Payments to the Unemployment Insurance Fund, 1985 (Box 14 (9-Legislation), Folder 128)
  - Plattsburgh Air Force Base Traffic Laws, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - Confidentiality Protections of Out-of-State Information, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - Clarify the Powers and Duties of the Sentencing and Receiving Court, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - Reproduction of Hospital Records, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - Provide a Discovery Statute of Limitations Rule for Toxic Torts, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - Permission to Appeal may not be Sought from a Non-Participating Judge, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - Damages for Pain and Suffering may only be Rewarded with Permanent Injury where Medical Expenses Exceeds $2,500, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - Require Written Franchise Agreements between Brewers and Wholesalers, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - Establishing a Division of Law Enforcement in the DEC, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 9)
  - Procedures following Verdict or Plea of Not Responsible by Reason of Mental Disease or Defect, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - Allow the Crime Victims Board to Investigate Claims of Alleged Acts of Person with Court Sealed Records, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - Addition of "Offenses Involving Computers", 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - Requires All Peace Officers to Receive the Same Basic Training, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - Division of Parole Peace Officers, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - Purchase of Military Service Credit by New York State Retirement System Members, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - Prohibit Multiple Purchases of Big Game Licenses by One Person, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 16)
  - Exclude Pinball, Video, and Similar Machines from Definition of Gambling Devices, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - Deer Management Permits, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 18)
  - Minimum Age for Small Game Hunting, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - Provide Favorable and Equitable Tax Treatment for Forest Owners Implementing the Approved Forest Management Practices, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - APA Membership Total Increase, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - Adirondack Park Local Government Review Board Staff and Allotments, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - Repeal Tax Exemption for Subsidized Railroad Property, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - Exempt Certain Small Businesses from Boiler Inspections, 1985 (Box 15 (9-Legislation), Folder 24)